Guide to the Mildred Warner papers, 1997-2006
Warner, Mildred papers
- 50 State Model (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Percentile Histogram Type 1 Output Multiplier, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Percentile Histogram Type 2 Employment Multiplier, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Percentile Histogram Type 2 Output Multiplier, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 1 Output, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 2 Output, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 1 Gross Receipts, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 2 Gross Receipts, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 1 Employment, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Regression Type 2 Employment, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Comments on model Jim Pratt, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Summary tentative model with p less than 10 and signs of independent variables, September 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Meeting notes discussion on model Sept. 29, September 29, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Memo 50 State Model presentation in Binghamton Rose Ribeiro, October 1, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 50 state map with data run state employment multiplier, October 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 50 state map with data run state output multiplier, October 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Model variable outliers, October 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Outline for 50 state model paper, March 5, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting notes model components Mar 24, March 24, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting notes regional purchase coefficients, April 7, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Outline 50 state model report (revised), April 8, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Meeting notes discussion of model Apr 9, April 9, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Policy brief outline proposals, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Figure 4.1 Proposed input/output matrix, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression output Type 2 without new variables, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression output Type 2 with gross absorption coefficient of child care and service sector RPC, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression output Type 2 with only Implan variables, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression employment Type 2 without new variables, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression employment Type 2 with gross absorption coefficient and RPC for services, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression employment Type 2 with only Implan variables, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression gross receipts child care, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression gross receipts with gross absorption coefficient and RPC services, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Regression gross receipts with median output multiplier, median employment multiplier, gross absorption coefficient and RPC services, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Child care regression model, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Email for child care production function meeting, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Email and attachments regarding use of regional purchase coefficients in IMPLAN models, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Email and attachments Rose Ribeiro model data files, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.5: Regression results and data run child care output, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.5: Regression results and data run child care output without med emp 2, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.5: Regression results and data run child care type II output multipliers, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.6 Regression results and data run child care type II employment multipliers, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.6: Regression results and data run child care employment, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Table 5.6 Regression results and data run Child care employment without med emp 2, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chapter Economic Linkage for the Child Care Sector, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Maps Regional Economic Linkage of the Child Care Sector by State-State type II output multipliers, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Maps Regional Economic Linkage of the Child Care Sector by State-State type II employment multipliers, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Final report, June 26, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- CRP 418/618-ARME 634 Spring, 2004 and Related Child Care Work (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Course announcement and syllabus, January 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Class Roster, January 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Reading List, January 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Summary of economic impact studies, January 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Child Care and Economic Development Presentation University of Wisconsin, February 9, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Summary: Financing Child Care in the United States-Shira Adriance, February 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Summary: Financing Child Care in the Private Sector, February 13, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Revised class timeline, March 8, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Annotated Bibliography of articles pertaining to state budget crisis, March 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Annotated Bibliography of articles pertaining to child care and productivity, March 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Responses for interview requests, March 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Interview suggestions, March 12, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Taryn Morrisey summary of market failure and child care with comments from Mildred Warner, March 18, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Economic Development Primer outline and chapter contents, March 31, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Market failures in the child care sector drafts, March 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Outline comments from Louise Stoney, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Ellen Pratt interview notes, April 2, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Louise Stoney interview notes, April 2, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - David Foster interview notes, April 2, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Jen Wohl interview notes, April 2, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Janice Gruendel interview notes, April 5, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Class notes Apr 7, April 7, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Child care economic development primer final draft, April 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Meeting notes workshop outline, June 15, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Various emails and correspondence on confernce, Summer 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Meeting notes Walter Israel, August 10, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Conference Invitations, October 27, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Final Economic Development Strategy Guide, December 1, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Proposal for Meeting Facilitation and realted documents, December 14, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Correspondence to conference presenters, December 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Email Midlred Warner on abstracts, December 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Email Suzanna Montreal, February 10, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Draft Confernce Agenda, February 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Unpublished conference paper How Regional Economists Measure the Economic Importance of Local Economic Sectors: Implications for the Child Care Industry Thomas Johnson, April 19, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Conference Agenda, May 16, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Conference Agenda, May 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Participant list Economic Significance of the Child Car Sector workshop, May 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Various notes on conference presentations, May 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Unpublished conference paper Hypothetical Extraction and Child Daycare Services: The Role of Hypothetical Extraction in Measuring Economic Significance Michael Lahr, May 17, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Email to Ted Bradshaw special issue on conference material, May 20, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Econ Dev Strat Guide brochure, Fall 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Community Development Special Issue on Child Care and Community Development, Spring 2006 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
- Invest in Kids Partnership and Associated Materials (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rough outline for paper on Receiving High Returns on Early Childhood Development, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rough outline for paper on Receiving High Returns on Early Childhood Development with notes, January 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Draft: Early Childhood Development: Economic Development with a High Public Return by Rolnick and Grunewald, January 24, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Draft: A Proposal for Achieving High Returns on Early Childhood Development by Rolnick and Grunewald, December 24, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Review notes by Mildred Warner to Rolnick and Grunewald on paper, February 2, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Invitation and notes for Committee of Economic Development's Building the Economic Case for Investments in Preschool meeting, October 4, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Meeting notes for discussion of fiscal impacts of universal pre-k with applicable literature and presentations, April 25, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Invest in Kids Partnership (Proposal Creating a Children-First Nation and a First-Class Economy, December 1, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Invest in Kids Partnership (Proposal Creating a Children-First Nation and a First-Class Economy with additional notes, December 1, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Agenda: Building the Economic Case for Investments in Preschool Meeting, January 10, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Partnership for America's Economic Success: Investing in Children request for research proposals, January 13, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Email and attachment PAES Advisory Board update and request for comment on finance polices, August 3, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CRP 418/618-ARME 634 Spring, 2006 NYS Econ Dev Conference (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
  - Background: Executive Summary: Employment, workplace practices, and labor-management relations in Western New York, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Child Care Multipliers: Analysis from Fifty States, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Building a Two-Lane High Road: Unions and Economic Development in Western New York, Summer 2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - WEDA Member survey, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Labor and Urban Crisis in Buffalo, New York: Building a High Road Infrastructure, March 30, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Champions Network: Buffalo Niagara Labor-Business-Community Alliance for High Road Economics, Spring 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Cornell University Life Quality News, Fall 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background: Agenda Economic Development Summit at Cornell, November 10, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting notes Carol Saginaw to discuss course Jan 14, January 4, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Course announcement and syllabus, January 13, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class Roster, January 13, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting notes Carol Saginaw conference discussion Jan 26, January 26, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class notes Jan 27, January 27, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting notes Jan 31, January 31, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class notes Feb 1, February 1, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class notes Feb 3, February 3, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class proposals for conference, February 7, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Email Carol Saginaw interest in conference, February 7, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Memo to Carol Saginaw Conference Logistics, February 13, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Transportation brief, February 24, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence from Barbara Lifton to Seldon Silver, February 27, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Conference assignments, February 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Notes: case study suggestion, March 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - List of March conference calls, March 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Memo to Carol Saginaw Conference logistics and alternatives, March 1, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class notes Mar 8, March 8, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting agenda March 9, March 9, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Email to Carol Saginaw on conference costs, March 15, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Notes on transportation brief rewrite, March 27, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Primary Child Care Arrangements of Employed Parents - Cappizzano and Main 2002, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Class notes with timeline and survey suggestions Mar 28, March 28, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes Mar 31, March 31, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tentative list of confirmed speakers with notes on each speaker, March 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Estimate conference cost, April 11, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Economic Development Planning Brief, April 12, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Conference invitation and registration form, April 13, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes Apr 19, April 19, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes Apr 28, April 28, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Revised conference agendas, April 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Preliminary survey results, April 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Email Carol Saginaw participation of Kathryn Ozimek, May 1, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes May 3, May 3, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes with survey results May 5, May 5, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Class notes May 12, May 12, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cultivating Connections: The Cornell 2006 Survey on Economic Development and Child Care, May 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cultivating Connections: Issue Brief: Labor Force Trends and the Role of Child Care in New York, May 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Misc notes (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Complete Conference Folder with participant list and all conference materials and notes, May 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)